let questions = [
  {
    question: 'O que você gosta de comer?',
    options:[
      'What you like to eat?',
      'What does you like to eat?',  
      'What do you like to eat?'
    ],
    answer:2
  },
  {
    question: 'Onde Ana estuda inglês?',
    options:[
      'Where do Ana study English?',
      'Where does Ana studies English?',  
      'Where does Ana study English?'
    ],
    answer:2
  },
  {
    question: 'Quando nós temos que voltar?',
    options:[
      'When do we have to return?',
      'When we have to return?',  
      'When does we has to return?'
    ],
    answer:0
  },
  {
    question: 'Por que você assiste anime?',
    options:[
      'Why you watch anime?',
      'Why do you watch anime?',  
      'Why do you watches anime?'
    ],
    answer:1
  },
  {
    question: 'Quem sabe meu nome?',
    options:[
      'Who knows my name?',
      'Who do knows my name?',  
      'Who does know my name?'
    ],
    answer:0
  },
  {
    question: '__________ does Andrew do for a living?',
    options:[
      'Where',
      'What',     
      'When'
    ],
    answer:1
  },
  {
    question: '__________ do you study english?',
    options:[
      'Who',
      'What',     
      'Where'
    ],
    answer:2
  },
  {
    question: '__________ does Katherine have so many cats?',
    options:[
      'Why',
      'How many',     
      'When'
    ],
    answer:0
  },
  {
    question: '__________ does have problem with this subject?',
    options:[
      'What',
      'Who',     
      'Why'
    ],
    answer:1
  },
  {
    question: '__________ do you want your coffee, ma`am?`',
    options:[
      'How',     
      'What',
      'How much'
    ],
    answer:0
  },  
]